hello all happy New Year the audiovisual
production project at The Institute the
one that brings you all the live streams
and podcasts is seeking participants for
2025 if you might like to get more
involved at The Institute and contribute
to the applicability rigor and awareness
of active inference this is a great
Hands-On opportunity or are you watching
on YouTube and want to help from the
other side of the fourth
wall no specific technal teal background
or expertise in active inference is
required a good fit for a volunteer on
this project would be an internally
motivated learner who is familiar with
or wanting to upskill on tasks related
to audiovisual processing and
accessibility facilitation sector
research human intelligence open source
llm transcription translation methods
art media
performance and more we have a podcast
and stream scheduling checklist specific
procedures for inviting guests and
recording events so there are
streamlined direct modular ways to help
with this project it is possible to play
roles ranging from surfacing and
inviting exciting guests on through
facilitating live or recorded
sessions and even designing a series of
your own for example as da I did with
the active inference insights as Sarah
did with the morph stream and as shanana
did with the math art Series so in
closing working on the production
project is a meaningful way to have
broad impact in the active inference
ecosystem and Beyond while following
your curiosity and passion developing
useful skills and helping others learn
through deep time to get involved or ask
any questions email blanket at active
inference do Institute with the subject
line production thank you Daniel January
9th 2025